doctor came to you said
he couldn't play sports said
he wouldn't be able to
say I love you to
you. Yeah that must have
been heartbreaking was terribly heartbreaking
and but I was stuck
in denial for for a
period of time I really
was and I talk about
that in my book of
just being that that father
and that man that wanted
to fix my son and
really didn't him and so
for a period of time
we didn't connect and she
was rolling up her sleeve
she was reading every book
she was talking to families
she was talking to doctors
and she was sending me
books and I throw them
under my bed not read
them and it came to
a point where I really
had to almost get embarrassed
by the treatment that was
given to him and understand
that I needed to really
put away all my expectations
really come down to his
level and understand what autism
is. I went on the
war path and he you
know sort of retreated and
so I'm really blessed that
we were able to meet
in the middle and I
think Roddy's book not things
that are early on our
doctor said he would never
ever do and so we're
lucky in that respect